[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Grease 2 come out?", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1986", "1980", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the theme song for the movie Aladdin?", "correct_answer": "Arabian Nights", "incorrect_answers": ["Friend Like Me", "A Whole New World", "Aladdin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of meat product is used for the preparation of Buffalo wings?", "correct_answer": "Chicken wings", "incorrect_answers": ["Pork ham", "Buffalo ribs", "Chopped pork"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Sam and Lucys last name in the movie I Am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Dawson", "incorrect_answers": ["Daley", "Dallas", "Dale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a sound made by cheetahs?", "correct_answer": "Roar", "incorrect_answers": ["Hiss", "Yelp", "Purr"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In how many ways can ough be pronounced in English?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "13", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the race of humans that fought against the Fellowship and their Allies in Lord of the Rings?", "correct_answer": "Easterlings", "incorrect_answers": ["Noldorin", "M\u00fbmakil", "Istari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Bronte sisters wrote the famous novel Jane Eyre?", "correct_answer": "Charlotte Bronte", "incorrect_answers": ["Anne Bronte", "Elizabeth Bronte", "Emily Bronte"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Should you feed a small dog, such as a miniature poodle, the same amount of food you should a large dog, for example a great dane?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many species of trilobite existed over the duration of the Paleozoic?", "correct_answer": "17,000", "incorrect_answers": ["12,000", "9,000", "18,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to data from the year 2001, crocodiles were the second leading cause of animal related death worldwide, second to venomous snakes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is regarded as  The first Latin lover?", "correct_answer": "Rudolph Valentino", "incorrect_answers": ["Ricardo Montalban", "Antonio Moreno", "Miguel de Servantez"]}]